Annual Reports; Collection ua932
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Annual Reports Collection
1844-2005
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York at Albany
ua932
0.83 cubic ft.
Collection is made up of annual reports from the Executive Committee and President of the College as well as several reports presented to the President of the College.
Administrative History
The New York State Normal School was first opened in 1844, and presented yearly reports on the state of the school to the government. These reports have been given yearly by the President of the schoool or the executive committee of the college and given to the Legislature of the State of New York.
Scope and Contents
Collection is made up of the annual reports from the school dating from the years 1844-2005. These encompass the full existence of the school, though some years are missing, such as the majority of the 1850s. The reports include the state of the school, number of graduates, financial reports, and enrollment lists.
Additional reports from the 1990s provided to the President's Office on topics including affirmative and academic outcomes are included in this collection as well.
Arrangement of the Collection
Collection is arranged chronologically.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Educational reports; College graduates; College presidents; UAlbany Reference Collections
- Report of the Committees on Colleges, 1844 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 1)
- Annual Report of the Executive Committee, 1846 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 2)
- Annual Report of the Executive Committee, 1848 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 3)
- New York State College for Teachers Application Form, Undated (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 4)
- Notice of Vacancies of the State Normal School, 1851 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 5)
- Annual Report of the Executive Committee, 1863 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 6)
- Annual Report of the Executive Committee, 1864 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 7)
- Annual Report of the Executive Committee, 1865 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 8)
- Annual Report of the Executive Committee, 1866 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 9)
- Annual Report of the Executive Committee, 1867 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 10)
- Annual Report of the Executive Committee, 1868 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 11)
- Annual Report of the Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1869 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 12)
- Annual Report of the Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1872 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 13)
- Annual Report of the Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1873 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 14)
- Annual Report of the Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1873 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 15)
- Annual Report of the Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1874 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 16)
- Annual Report of the Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1876 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 17)
- Annual Report of the Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1877 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 18)
- Annual Report of the Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1878 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 19)
- Annual Report of the Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1879 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 20)
- Annual Report of the Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1880 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 21)
- Annual Report of the Executive Committee, 1880 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 22)
- Annual Report of the Executive Committee, 1881 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 23)
- Annual Report of the Executive Committee, 1882 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 24)
- Annual Report of the Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1884 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 25)
- Annual Report of the Executive Committee, 1885 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 26)
- State Normal School Announcement, 1883 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 27)
- New York State Documents on State Normal School, Undated (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 28)
- Superintendent of Common Schools, 1853-1902 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 29)
- Annual Report of the Executive Committee, 1886 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 30)
- Annual Register, 1864 (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 31)
- List of Executive Committee Minutes, Undated (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 32)
- State Normal School Publications List, Undated (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 33)
- Catalogue of the Officers and Students, Undated (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 34)
- List of Students, Undated (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 35)
- Term Numbers and Dates List, Undated (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 36)
- State Normal College Circular, Undated (Box 1 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 37)
- Report of the New York State Normal College, 1912 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 1)
- President's Report, 1915-1916 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 2)
- President's Report, 1917 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 3)
- President's Report, 1933 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 4)
- President's Report, 1934 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 5)
- President's Report, 1935 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 6)
- President's Report, 1936 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 7)
- President's Report, 1937 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 8)
- President's Report, 1938 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 9)
- President's Report, 1939 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 10)
- President's Report, 1948 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 11)
- President's Report, 1970 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 12)
- President's Report, 1986 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 13)
- President's Report, 1987 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 14)
- President's Report, 1988 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 15)
- President's Report, 1989 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 16)
- President's Report, 1990 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 17)
- President's Report, 1991 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 18)
- President's Report, 1992 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 19)
- President's Report, 1993 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 20)
- President's Report, 1994 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 21)
- President's Report, 1995 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 22)
- President's Report, 1996 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 23)
- President's Report, 1997 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 24)
- President's Report, 1998 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 25)
- President's Report, 1999 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 26)
- President's Report, 2000 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 27)
- President's Report, 2001 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 28)
- President's Report, 2002 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 29)
- President's Report, 2003 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 30)
- President's Report, 2004 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 31)
- President's Report, 2005 (Box 2 (Annual Reports Collection), Folder 32)